你被炒了
You're fired.
《我们的生活》前情提要
Previously on This Is Us...
-什么  -也许我们该奋斗各自的事业了
- What? - I think it's time we go at it alone for a while.
字幕组
ZiMuZu.tv
就一段时间  看结果如何
You know? See what happens.
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
最新最快海外影视字幕下载
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv
抱歉  我的剧本上没写有停顿...
This doesn't say "Pause" on my script.
上面也没写烂呢  再看现在这个效果
Well, it doesn't say "suck" either, yet here we are.
■
翻译:  青椒  moonshine7  小萝莉  Tracy-旋子
我根本不是演戏剧的料
I'm not cut out for theater.
你总是这样  怀疑自己
You do that a lot-- doubt yourself.
翻译:  小尼克  小应子  桑葚  冬麟  克里斯
你们一直忙着不让凯特吃得太多
You're so busy making sure that Kate's not eating too much...
凯文  冷静一下
Kev, calm down.
总怕兰德尔觉得自己是被领养的
...and Randall's not too adopted!
校对:  兔牙Bobby猫  不高兴童鞋
对不起  我本该在你身边的  以后改正
I'm sorry. I should have been there, and I'm gonna be there.
我儿子平时放学后
Do you think that my son could play with
时间轴:  格瑞特  ccisoda
-能跟你家小孩一起玩吗  -当然
- yours sometime after school? - Yeah.
每次我新认识一个黑人
Every time I met a new black person,
后期:  宝宝  精校&总监:  红枫Gabriel
就在那个小本本上标记一下
I would put a mark in this notebook,
每次遇见一个黑人男子
and every time I met a black man,
我就会想他会不会是我亲生父亲
I wondered if that man could possibly be my father.
不行  宝贝  要先吃完香蕉
No, baby, you got to finish your bananas first.
想吃香蕉吗  小凯  吃香蕉吗
You want some banana? Kev, you want a little banana, too?
吃完就可以去找爸爸玩了  再吃点
Go in and see your daddy right now, okay? You have some more.
-杰克  牛奶好像没了  -好
- Jack, I think we're completely out of milk. - Yeah.
-他就是不喝果汁  -行  我...
- He won't drink his juice. - Yeah, I'll, um...
-就想喝牛奶  -我下次带点回来
- He just wants milk. - I'll bring some home.
要再吃点苹果吗  来吧
Do you want some more apples? Come on.
来  吃饱了要不要下来  好的
Come on. Here, do you want to get out of your chair? Yeah.
来吧
All right. Come on.
亲爱的  你要去做文职
Babe, a desk job?
小贝  我们需要这份工资
Bec, we need the money.
你连领带都没有
You don't even own a tie.
三个小家伙之家
话说
So...
你听说了吗
did you hear?
听说了
Uh... yeah.
要在茶水间给桑德拉准备惊喜生日蛋糕
Surprise birthday cake for Sandra in the break room.
其实根本算不上什么惊喜
You know, it's never, it's never a surprise.
还有一件事
Okay, also,
我升职了
I got promoted.
现在是项目经理了
Project manager.
-太好了  恭喜你  -谢谢
- That's great, man. Hey. - Thanks.
我想带你一起
And I'm bringing you with me.
这个...
Oh. Um...
谢谢你  不过算了
thanks, but no.
-还是谢谢你  -怎么算了
- But thanks. - No?
你先别声张
Keep this quiet,
我准备自己出去闯
but I'm, uh, gonna go out on my own.
想自己创业
I want to start my own thing.
我知道很冒险  但是只要事业步入正轨
I know it's risky, but once I get things up and running,
我就能有更多时间陪孩子们了
I can spend more time with my kids.
好吧  要不这样  先别急着拒绝
All right, how 'bout this: why don't you, um,
花几天时间考虑一下
take till the end of the week,
-周末再答复我  -真的不用了
- think about it. - I'm okay.
我不需要考虑
Don't need to think.
周末再说  好吗
End of the week, okay?
成绩单
-爸爸回来了  -回来了
- Daddy's home! - Hi!
爸爸  爸爸
Dad! Dad!
-爸爸  -小凯别闹
- Dad! - Kev.
-爸爸  -小凯
-小子  -我有问题要问你
- Hi. Hey, buddy. - I need to ask you a question...
-稍等  -爸爸
- One second. - Dad!
-你快看  -已经做得这么漂亮啦
- Watch this. - Hey, look-look at the progress you made, bud.
-吃完晚饭就帮你  好吗  -宝贝
- I'm gonna help you out after dinner, okay? - Hi. Hi, baby.
-爸爸  -怎么了
- Dad! - Yeah.
-我们有冰淇淋吃啦  -冰淇淋
- We're getting ice cream! - Ice cream!
-冰淇淋  -我答应他们的
- Ice cream? - I promised them.
冰淇淋  冰淇淋
Ice cream? Ice cream?!
又不是给我买的  不然你下次就抱不动我了
None for me if you want to be able to pick me up again.
瞎说  你这么瘦
Please, you are tiny.
-就你嘴甜  -不过你答应买冰淇淋
- Right. Mm. - But ice cream must mean that the kids'
-是不是因为孩子们成绩挺好  -没有
- report cards came back and they were good? - No.
基本都是B和C  我没辙了
Actually, mostly B's and C's. I caved.
不知道该怎么办  我额叶都疼了
I don't know. Parenting makes my cerebellum hurt.
你的什么
Sorry, your what?
就是我的大脑中控制情绪的部分
It's the part of my brain that makes my emotions.
我做了太多三年级的科学作业了
I have been doing way too much third grade science homework.
不过你还是看看这个吧
But why don't you, uh, look at that.
兰德尔的老师为什么想见我们
Why does Randall's teacher want to see us?
不知道
I don't know.
好吧
Okay.
*你如此美丽*
*You are too beautiful*
*亲爱的  我想对你说*
*My dear, to be true*
*我如此愚钝*
*For one lucky fool*
*配不上你*
*To be with*
*你太过美丽*
*You are too beautiful*
*我如此愚钝*
*And I am a fool*
*却爱慕着你*
*For beauty*
恕我冒昧  如果太久不弹  钢琴会很孤单
Hope you don't mind. Pianos get forlorn if you don't play 'em.
不  我完全不介意
No, of course I don't mind.
-你怎么学会弹钢琴的  -我爸教我的
- Where'd you learn how to play like that? - My dad taught me.
我爸是他爸教的
And his dad taught him.
爸爸  你能教我们弹琴吗
Dad, can you teach us to play?
我也很想教
I wish I could.
可家里的音乐细胞都被奶奶和凯特姑姑占了
Grandma and Aunt Kate got all the music talent in the family.
我一向都只有肌肉发达
Me? I was always all knuckles.
你爸比较擅长其他方面
Yeah, well, your dad's got other skills.
以前我还能靠这个本事
Me, I managed to squeak out a couple of dollars
混几口饭吃
on one of these back in the day.
主要是吹小号  什么表演我都参加
Mostly trumpet, mm. Any gigs I could get.
你能不能来参加学校的职业日
Will you speak at my career day?
职业日能不能叫爷爷去
Can Grandpa speak at my career day?
我想不行  宝贝儿
I don't think so, baby.
只能一个人发言  我已经报名了
You're only allowed one speaker, and I'm already signed up.
我想让爷爷讲
I pick Grandpa.
他的工作很酷
He had a cool job.
你是说老爸的工作就不酷了吗
What are you saying, that Daddy doesn't have a cool job?
你们很喜欢到办公室找我玩  不是吗
But you guys love visiting me at the office, right?
我喜欢坐在你的椅子上转圈
I like spinning in your chair.
其实你的工作有点无聊  爸爸
You kind of have a boring job, Dad.
基于长期气候模式的商品期货交易
Trading commodity futures based on long-term weather patterns
才不会无聊  好吗
is not boring, okay?
抱歉
Sorry,
一听"商品"这个词我就有点犯困
sort of fell asleep soon as I heard the word "commodity."
凯文叔叔  你能在我的职业日上发言吗
Uncle Kevin, can you speak at my career day?
老爸会负责职业日  讨论到此结束
Daddy's doing career day! End of discussion.
我的发言会很"燃"的
And it's gonna be lit.
"燃"这个字不是这么用的  对吧
That's not how you use "lit," right?
对
No.
对不起  我不明白
Sorry, I don't understand.
你们是说兰德尔很有天分吗
So you are saying that Randall is gifted?
可他成绩很一般啊
But his grades are average.
你确定给他做的测试没问题吗
Are you sure you tested him right?
杰克  我们知道他有多聪明
Jack, we know how smart he is.
那他的成绩是怎么回事
Okay, so what's up with his grades?
也许是...  老师对他有偏见
M-Maybe is the-the teacher prejudiced?
-杰克  -不可能
- Jack. - No.
如果孩子在测试中表现良好
When a child tests well
成绩却反映不出来
but his grades don't seem to reflect it,
通常是他所在的学校没有足够的挑战
oftentimes, he isn't being challenged at his school.
或许你们可以考虑其他选择
And you maybe want to consider other options.
海恩斯学院
招收超常儿童
他们对兰德尔这类特殊儿童
They have wonderful programs
由一套出色的学习方案
for exceptional children like Randall.
绝对不行
Not gonna happen.
杰克  你能不能冷静点
Jack, please stop making me say "Jack."
虽然兰德尔在的这所学校只有几个黑人孩子
Randall is one of the only black kids at this school,
可他在这儿至少还有兄弟姐妹
but at least here he has his brother and sister.
-我明白  -那另外两个孩子呢
- I know. - What about them?
他们也能去那所学校吗
I mean, can they go, too?
皮尔森先生  恕我冒昧
Mr. Pearson, all due respect,
凯文和凯特过去是没什么好处的
Kevin and Kate wouldn't do well in that school.
看到没  这就是你们犯的错误
You see, that's where you're wrong.
我们的三个孩子都很出众
All of our children are exceptional.
我能摸摸你吗
Can I touch you?
我只想再触摸你一次
I just want to touch you one more time.
哪怕...  只是你身体的一部分
Just... one part of your body.
你的头发
Your hair.
我想清醒过来
I want to wake up...
对不起  我...  我...
I'm sorry, I... I'm...
我不能...
I'm not...
对不起  可以重来一遍吗
I'm sorry, can we... can we just start over?
好的  凯文  能问你个问题吗
Yeah, yeah. Uh, Kevin, can I ask you something?
当然
Yeah.
为什么...
Why...
你能不能试着给我解释一下
Just try to help me understand this.
为什么每到这个场景
Wh-Why, every time we come to this scene,
这场戏悲伤到极点  本应该...
this-this pinnacle of grief, which should rip...
我是说  你本该让观众们痛哭流涕
I mean, literally rip... tears from the audience,
你语气怎么像谷歌地图的语音一样毫无感情呢
why you summon up all the emotion of a Google Maps voice.
好吧
Right.
我不知道  可能...
I don't know. May...
可能台词有问题
You know, maybe it's in the words.
你怎么知道
How would you know?
你从没说过那段词
You've never said them.
没有啊  我...  我正说着呢
Uh, no, I think... I think I'm saying 'em.
不对  你是  说了几句
No. I mean, yeah, like, s-some.
说了点
Kind of.
可你大多都改了
But you're-you're mostly paraphrasing.
-对不起  -没事没事
- I'm sorry. - Y-Yeah.
你看  其实很简单
You see, it's really simple.
奥利维亚就是杰西卡  你的妻子
Olivia is Jessica, your wife.
-又来了  -你就是大卫
- Okay. - You are David.
你爱她
You loved her,
可现在她死了
but now she is dead.
所以你正为失去她而悲痛不已
So you are grieving the loss of her.
你的世界都崩塌了
There's no longer any such thing as gravity.
你有没有失去过什么人
Have you ever lost anyone?
有
Yes.
可我不相信你
Because I don't believe you.
知道吗  罗恩  我的工作
Well, you know, Ron, it's not my job
不是要让你来相信我
to make sure you believe me.
不  不对  就是这样
Oh, yes, yes, it is! It is!
这就是你的事
It is exactly your job!
做好你该做的事
Do your job.
她在写什么
What is she writing?
你写什么呢
What are you writing?
写她的绝命书
That's her suicide note.
好了  好了  你们都够了  好吗
All right, all right, enough, okay?
他能做到的
He'll get there.
好吧
Okay.
好
All right.
周二上午十点  大家再来
10:00 A.M. Tuesday, everybody.
-多谢你  -只是必要的过程
- Thank you. - It's a process.
先别再想了
Just... let it go for now.
好
Yeah.
你明天有什么安排
What are you doing tomorrow?
我打算花一整天时间
Oh. Uh, well, tomorrow I was just gonna spend
感受我的失败  不过...
the entire day feeling like a failure, but, uh...
跟我去派对吧
Come to a party with me.
派对  你说什么派对
A party? What kind of party we talking?
-我会把地址发给你  -好吧
- I'll text you the address. - Yeah, okay. All right.
我去  不是吧
There's no way in hell.
这工作最好值得我费劲爬上去
This job better be worth it.
再见了  世界
See ya, world.
以前的日子真好
It's been real.
天啊
Oh, Jesus.
你真的没事吗
You sure you're all right?
对  我很好
Oh. Yeah, I'm good.
我很好  真的
I'm good. Yeah. Yeah.
没事
I'm good.
罗森塔尔太太
Mrs. Rosenthal...
叫我马琳
Marin.
马琳
Oh. Marin.
我知道我之前在我哥哥手下的工作经历
I realize that my previous employment with my brother
可能和这份工作不是很相符
might not be directly applicable.
可是我这人做事条理分明
However, I am abnormally organized.
1997年美国电影
男主角患有洁癖强迫症并憎恶同性恋
我就是《尽善尽美》中
And I'm basically the not crazy version
正常版的杰克·尼科尔森
of Jack Nicholson in As Good as It Gets.
-我超喜欢那部电影  -是吗
- Oh, I love that movie. Oh. - Right?
"你让我想成为更好的人"
"You make me want to be a better man."
抱歉
Oh! Sorry.
抱歉  你刚才说...
I'm sorry, you were saying...
对  我有补助金的写作经验
No. I-I have grant writing experience,
而且经常和好莱坞的一些人打交道
and I'm used to dealing with Hollywood types,
我知道他们是你们基金的主要捐助者
which I know are large contributors to your foundation.
我还知道  你是"保持联络"
And I know you're on the board of Stay In Touch
和"蝴蝶舞会"的董事会成员
and the Butterfly Ball.
我的天  真是太厉害了
Oh, my God, that's amazing.
作家  艺术家  木偶表演家
道格·金凯德
Doug Kincaid,
在你哥哥之前  他是你老板  对吗
your boss before your brother, was it?
他对你称赞有加
He speaks about you in such glowing terms.
你为什么要离开他的公司
Why did you quit his firm?
因为我爱上了他
Because I fell in love with him,
所以我们不适合一起工作
and it was not a healthy situation.
我喜欢你  凯特
I like you, Kate.
你能胜任  你很聪明
You're qualified, you're smart,
而我现在正需要一个助手
and I need someone right now by my side.
但并不是做助理的工作
Now, it's not assistant work.
既要协调活动  又要拓展业务
It's part event coordinator, part development associate.
荣幸之至
I would be absolutely thrilled.
不过你可能还得替我办些私事
But there is some personal stuff you may have to do,
有时跑跑腿
an errand here or there,
开车接送我女儿
maybe drive my daughter to and from?
好啊  没问题
Yeah. Okay.
-偶尔的  所以别担心  -当然不会
- Not much, so don't worry about that. - No, of course.
那么  你接受这份工作吗
So, do you want the gig?
等等  真的吗
Wait, really?
我太激动了
I'm so excited!
我也很激动
Well, I'm so excited!
从卫生纸粘住你头的那一刻起
I wanted you from the moment
我就已经决定要你了
the toilet paper was stuck to your head.
说真的  不管你需要什么
Seriously, though, whatever you need,
我都愿意去做
I'm your girl.
这是我女儿  杰玛  这位是凯特
This is my daughter. Jemma, this is Kate.
你雇了个胖子啊
So, I see you picked the fat one.
我们的生活
第一季  第六集
天气衍生品是一种贸易商品
Weather derivatives are tradable commodities
它能够保护企业所有者
that protect business owners
免受天气变化的影响
from future changes in the weather.
就好比你舔一下披萨
It's like licking a piece of pizza
别人就不会吃了
so that nobody will eat it later.
我开始想披萨了
Now I'm thinking about pizza.
-好吧  -不  等等  抱歉  等一下
- Okay. - No, wait, I'm sorry-- no, no, no, wait,
我这次是想搞清楚的
I was gonna get it this time.
如果连我的老婆孩子都不理解我是做什么的
Look, how am I supposed to inspire an auditorium full of strangers,
我又怎么能打动一个礼堂的陌生人呢
and my own wife and kids don't even understand what I do?
-不是这样的  -真的吗
- That's not true. - Really?
我是做什么的
What do I do?
你买卖天气
You trade weather.
你根据天气类型交易商品
You trade commodities based on weather patterns.
这又是什么意思呢
And what does that mean?
该死  兰德尔  我不知道
Oh, damn, Randall, I don't know.
你用闪电球交换雷暴云
You swap lightning bolts for thunder clouds?
我知道你每天都是怎么度过的
Look, I know what your day is like.
我知道你喜欢其中一个合伙人
I know that you like one of your partners
却讨厌另外一个
and you hate the other one.
我知道你打算重新设计办公室的家具
I know that you're gonna redesign your office furniture
你还有可能解雇你的助理
and that you might fire your assistant
因为她总是说"好像"
because she says "like" too much.
她说个不停
It's nonstop.
我能和你深入地探讨一下天气类型吗
Can I talk to you in depth about weather patterns?
不行  我做不到
No, I cannot.
即便我能  你也不会答应的  所以...
But I don't think you'd want me to if I could, so...
你到底怎么了
Hey, what's-what's this really about?
或许我本该成为一位音乐家
Maybe I was meant to be a musician.
不好意思  你说什么
I'm sorry, what now?
或者艺术家  或者作家
Or an artist or a writer.
想想看  贝丝
Just think about it, Beth.
也许我身上是有这种天赋的
There's this whole genetic side of me
只是根本没人发现
that nobody even knew existed.
我是说  威廉是个诗人
I mean, William was a poet,
艺术家  音乐家
an artist, a musician.
也许我一直很有艺术天赋
You know, maybe I've had an artistic side in me all along
可没人发掘出来
and nobody knew to empower it.
或许我不该做一个
You know, maybe I wasn't meant to be
每天必须西装革履
a straight and narrow math geek
中规中矩跟数字打交道的呆子
destined to wear a shirt and tie every day
就像我父母想象的那样
like my parents thought.
也许我这辈子就该做个音乐家
Maybe I was meant to live a musician's life.
到处奔走  在酒吧里演奏
On the road and playing clubs, you know?
好吧  在你这个音乐家的梦中
All right, well, in this musical fantasy version of yourself,
-你演奏哪种...  -萨克斯
- what instrument would you... - Sax.
1990年美国爵士乐电影
就像《爱情至上》中的韦斯利
Like Wesley in Mo' Better Blues.
一定得是萨克斯
Definitely sax.
是啊
Oh, yeah.
真是太性感了
That's sexy, yeah.
你在笑话我
You're making fun of me.
-没有  -有  你就是在笑话我
- No. - No, you're making fun of me.
不  没有  我没有啦
No, I am not. I'm-I'm not.
你亲生父亲刚回到你的生活中
Your biological father just came back into your life,
这激起了你的很多想法
and it's bringing up all kinds of stuff.
这  这很正常
It's-it's normal.
听着
Look,
你不妨试试展示下自己狂野艺术家的一面
why don't you try out this-this crazy artist side
在这次发言中一鸣惊人
of yourself and, you know, get this presentation popping.
看看八岁小观众们喜不喜欢  好吗
Let's see how it flies with some eight-year-olds, right?
在你真的改行
Before you, like, shift careers
去夜场演奏萨克斯风之前先实践下
and start playing open mic saxophone nights.
-也许我真会去  -那好啊
- You know, maybe I will. - Okay, yeah.
我知道你在笑话我  不过我会试试的
I see you are making fun of me, but I will.
没有  好啊
No, yeah.
-你能不能不笑了  -我停不下来
- Why don't you stop smiling? - I can't.
-别笑了  -抱歉
- Stop smiling. - I'm sorry.
我忍不住  这中年危机早期症状太像你了
This early midlife crisis is so you, I can't stand it.
你想再来点笑料吗
You want something to smile about?
-不要了  拜托  -真的  真的吗
- No, please. - Do you, do you really?
你好  麻烦找下麦克尔
Hi, can I speak to Michael please?
唐纳  我是凯特
Hey, Tanner, it's Kate.
对  凯文的妹妹  你最近怎么样
Yeah, Kevin's sister. How are you?
很好  想问下你会不会刚好有空
Oh, good. Are you by any chance
来参加个慈善会
available on the third for a charity event?
我有个问题想问下你
Hey, I have a question for you:
你对无家可归现象怎么看
how do you feel about homelessness?
我明白  很糟糕  对吧
I know, it's a bummer, right?
我们差不多要接待四百人
So, we're looking to cater about 400 people.
您的餐厅势必也想加入到我们的活动
Your restaurant's definitely gonna want to be a part of this.
天啊  我知道
Oh, my-- I know.
太棒了  行  很好
Awesome, okay, great.
谢谢  泽  拜拜
Thanks, Z. Bye.
你太能干了
You're killer.
我要你载我去艾希莉家
I need you to take me to Ashley's.
让凯特载你去怎么样
Oh, well, what if Kate gave you a ride?
可以吗
Do you mind?
行
No.
抱歉
Sorry.
我在车里等你  实习生
I'll be in the car, intern.
-要进去了吗  -好
- Should we go in? - Yeah.
这到底是个什么派对
Listen, what kind of party is this anyway?
大家看着都很难过的样子
'Cause everyone seems pretty sad.
当然难过了
Of course they're sad.
这是场追悼会
It's a memorial service.
快点  我们进去吧
Come on, in we go,
不然好吃的奶酪要没了
before all the good cheese is gone.
海恩斯学院
我们来这儿干嘛
What are we doing here?
我们来这
We are here
是因为你妻子  还记得她吗
because your wife-- do you remember her?
应该记得
I think so, yeah.
你爱她胜于生命的那个人
The one that you love more than life itself?
-想起来了  -那就好
- Definitely rings a bell. - Got it.
她想看看这地方
She wants to take a look at this place.
好吧  我在看呢
Okay, I'm looking.
天啊  这地方比兰德尔
Geez, this place is whiter
之前那满是白人的学校还要"白"啊
than Randall's already pretty white other school.
看看这些孩子
I mean, look at these kids.
他们就像小小的纳粹机器人
They look like little nazi robots.
那小孩还拎了个公文包
That one's got a briefcase.
我说  哪有孩子拎公文包的啊
I... no kid should be carrying a briefcase.
我觉得很可爱啊
I think it's cute.
是  你现在是觉得可爱  往后他余生
Yeah, it's cute now; next thing you know, he's gonna be
都要被困在办公室的小格子里了
trapped in a cubicle for the rest of his life.
我告诉你吧  先是拎个公文包
I tell you, it starts with a briefcase,
接着再系上个领带  坐上办公桌
then you put on a tie, you sit at a desk.
接下来你猜怎样  你就被束缚在日光灯下了
Next thing you know, you are so conditioned to the florescent lights
你走到外面  连太阳都会刺痛你的眼睛
that when you step outside, the sun actually burns your eyes.
真的吗
Really?
我说的不是自己
This isn't about me.
肯定也不是说兰德尔吧
Well, it certainly isn't about Randall.
我  我本来不打算在有初步规划前
Look, I... I wasn't gonna say anything
把事情说出来的  不过...
until I'd had a few details worked out, but...
我打算自己出来混了
I think I'm gonna go out on my own.
自己开公司
Start my own company.
三个小家伙之家  我只是...
Big Three Homes. I just...
现在说可能有点不合时宜
Doesn't feel like a very good time right now.
我觉得挺好的
I think it's great.
你应该去试试
I think you should do it.
没那么简单的  小贝
It's not that easy, Bec.
这个地方得花多少钱
I mean... what does this place even cost?
我们会想到办法的
We'll figure it out.
会有办法的  我们可以让兰德尔换一所学校
We'll figure it out-- we'll send Randall to another school,
给他请个家教  尽我们所能
we'll get him a tutor, we'll do whatever we have to do.
好  我只希望你能快乐
All right. I just don't want you to be unhappy.
-我说真的  -明白
- I mean it. - Okay.
那就好
All right.
我们会再回来的
We'll come back.
这儿很漂亮
This is nice.
非常漂亮
It's very nice.
杰玛  你妈妈说你会告诉我
Jemma, your mom told me that you would be giving me
艾希莉家的地址
Ashley's address.
杰玛  你能不能回答我的问题
Jemma, will you answer me?
杰玛  我需要地址
Jemma, I'm gonna need the address.
-干嘛  你急着回去工作吗  -是的
- Why? 'Cause you need to get back to work? - Yes.
要不是看重这份工作
And if I didn't value the work,
我也不会甘愿忍受你这态度了
I wouldn't be tolerating this attitude.
只是澄清下
Just so we're clear.
她跟你说什么了  让你当合伙人吗
What'd she tell you, you'd be an associate?
你真以为我妈妈会因为
And you thought my mom was gonna
一些三流明星接你的电话
give you actual responsibilities,
就给你真正的职位吗
because a few C-list celebrities take your calls?
很显然  她雇你
Clearly she only hired you
只是因为她觉得一个胖女孩会走进我的内心
because she thinks the fat girl can get through to me.
我猜她是觉得  越胖越好吧
Guess she figured, bigger the better.
其实我觉得你挺可怜的
You know, I actually feel bad for you.
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
你别可怜我  好吧
Yeah, well, don't feel bad for me, okay?
因为我还有车回家
'Cause I have a ride home.
什么意思
I'm sorry?
-下车  -什么
- Get out. - What?
给我下车  杰玛  不然我把你扔出去
Get out of the damn car, Jemma, before I toss you out of it!
你知道吗  你可以走路去艾希莉家
And you know what? You can walk to Ashley's.
给你分享胖女孩的心得  如果你走得快
And fat girl to fat girl, if you keep up the pace,
走路一小时可以燃烧417卡路里
you can burn 417 calories an hour walking.
我太爱美式奶酪了
I love American cheese.
英式奶酪吃起来总是很沮丧  太烦了
English cheese is so blue, it's angry.
美式奶酪就好像是可以躺上去的床
American cheese is like a-a bed you can just fall into.
话说回来  这是谁的告别聚会
So, whose good-bye party is this anyway?
弗兰克·彭德格拉斯
Frank Pendergrass.
三天前他在中央公园慢跑时
Tree branch fell on him three days ago
树枝砸在了他身上
when he was jogging through Central Park.
就这么死了
Bang. Dead.
这也太倒霉了
Well, that sucks.
你怎么认识他的
You knew him how?
我不认识  讣告上写了追悼会的地址
Oh, I didn't. No, the obituary gave the address of the service,
于是我就...
so, I thought...
等一下
Hold on a second.
你是什么意思
What are you trying to say?
你好
Hello.
我是弗兰克的妻子  格蕾丝
I'm Frank's wife, Grace.
你好  我叫杰西卡
Hi. Uh, I'm Jessica.
这是我丈夫  大卫
This is my husband, David.
你们是我丈夫的学生吗
Were you students of my husband?
我们其实是在他的课上相识的
We actually met in his class.
是吧
Right?
他学生
Students.
当时我们坐在第一排
Yeah, we were sitting in the front row,
一直眉来眼去的
and we kept looking at each other,
最后弗兰克看不下去了  停下来说道
and then finally Frank stopped the class and said,
"你们俩太让我分心了  出去  上个床
"You two are distracting me. Go outside, have sex,
准备好学知识了再进来"
and come back when you're ready to learn something."
还真像弗兰克会说的话
Well, that sounds like Frank.
弗兰克
Frank.
谢谢你们的到来
Thank you both so much for coming.
-感谢你的到来  -节哀顺变
- Thank you for coming. - I'm so sorry for your loss.
谢谢
Thank you.
任务完成了
Well done.
不不不  等等  你把我
No, no, no, hold on. No, no, no. You brought...
你把我带到一个陌生人的葬礼上来
You brought me to a stranger's funeral?
-追悼会  -管它叫什么  为什么
- Memorial service. - Whatever. Why
因为我演不好苦情戏吗
What, because I'm struggling with the grief scene?
你说过我会演好的
You said I would get there.
是啊  但我可没说凭你自己能演好
Yeah, well, I didn't say you'd get there on your own.
这也太疯狂了
This is insane.
但是十分感谢你的这一课
But thank you very much for the lesson.
我很感激  现在我要去喝杯酒
I appreciate it. Now I'm gonna go have a drink.
好好享受你的奶酪吧
Enjoy your cheese.
华特迪士尼于1967年制作并发行的动画电影
宝贝  怎么不看《森林王子》了
Hey, baby, what happened to Jungle Book?
演完了
It's over.
妈咪悄悄来洗个澡  嘘
Well, Mommy snuck in a quick shower-- shh.
一分一秒的时间都不能浪费呀  小可爱
Got to get them in while you can, little bug.
你真漂亮
You're so pretty.
谢谢  宝贝
Thank you, baby.
如果我漂亮你也漂亮  因为我们长得很像
Well, if I'm pretty, you're pretty, 'cause we look alike.
能不能把妈妈的黄色衬衣拿来
Oh, can you get Mommy's yellow blouse,
带纽扣的那件
the one with the buttons?
就在衣橱里  谢谢
Just in the closet? Thank you.
S号
XL号
谢谢  宝贝
Thank you, bug.
我去接兰德尔
Okay, I'm going to pick up Randall.
再见  小美人
Good-bye, beautiful.
一会儿见  宝贝  还有
Bye, see you later. Hey, baby,
我马上就准备好了
I'm almost done getting ready.
今晚  小家伙  我们一起拼B-52飞机
Tonight, little man, you, me and a B-52?
别做完了  我也要来拼一点
Okay, don't finish it, I got to help with something.
可以呀
Sounds good.
抱歉  我是在  我在...
I'm sorry. I was, I was, uh...
大家一直送我吃的  好像我不会做饭一样
People keep bringing me things, like I forgot how to cook.
冰箱都放不下了
There's no room in here
我也不知道把弗兰克的食物放哪儿
and I don't know where to put all of Frank's food.
好多腌黄瓜
You have a lot of pickles.
我讨厌腌黄瓜
I hate pickles.
但是他超爱的
But he loves them.
他在床上吃
Yeah, he eats them in bed.
曾经
"Ate."
现在他是过去式了
He is now past tense.
以前可以直呼其名
He used to be "is."
现在都要加个曾经
Now he is "was."
我喜欢腌黄瓜
Hey, I like pickles.
那太好了
Good.
-给你  -好
- Here. - OK.
你喜欢节日领带吗
How do you feel about holiday ties?
还有运动外套
And sport coats.
因为我问过杰里米了
Because I asked Jeremy,
他说不需要任何他爸爸的遗物
but he said he didn't want anything of his dad's.
杰里米多大了
How old is Jeremy?
十五岁
Fifteen.
这太残忍了
That's tough.
十五岁的话太残忍了
15 is tough.
我小时候
Uh, my dad and I
我和我爸会一起拼模型
used to build models together, when I was a kid.
是吗
Yeah?
是的  我们会拼飞机  轮船
Yeah, we'd build, um, planes and boats.
我以前总是挑最难的拼
I used to pick the most complex ones,
B-52轰炸机  航空母舰
B-52s, aircraft carriers,
因为做这些花的时间最长
'cause they took the longest, you know?
我们家有三个孩子
See, I was one of three kids,
所以真得花心思去争取和爸爸独处的时间
so you really had to strategize to get your alone time with Dad.
最后
You know, and eventually,
我们建了一整只舰队
we had a whole fleet of them;
一排一排地在架子上陈列着
We had just rows and rows, shelves of them.
当他去世以后...
You know, and then when he died...
当...
when...
当他去世后  我...
when he... when he died, I, um...
我把这些模型都扔掉了
I-I threw all the models away.
我把每一个都扔掉了
I threw every one of them away.
我也不知道我为什么要这样做
I don't know why... why I did that, you know?
那时你多大
You were how old?
那是很久以前了
Uh, it was a long time ago.
我还留着...
I have, um...
我还留着这个
I have this.
这个项链  这是他的
This necklace, this is his and, um,
我就只留了他这条链子
it's the only thing I have left of him.
最开始  我并不想戴
And at first, you know, I didn't want to wear it,
我不会戴  甚至都不想看  但现在...
I wouldn't wear it, I wouldn't even look at it, but now it's...
我只有这了  我不能取下来  所以...
It's all I have and I... I can't take it off now, so...
没事的
It's okay.
天哪  这实在太蠢了
Oh, my God, this is so dumb.
我在做什么  我该来安慰你才是
What am I doing? I'm supposed to be comforting you,
而不是把鼻涕流你身上到处都是
not snotting all over you.
你叫什么来着
Who are you again?
兰德尔  你爸爸来了
Randall, your daddy's here.
我们马上完了
We're almost done.
三局两胜
Best two out of three.
好
Okay.
谢谢你让他来你家玩
Hey, thanks for -- thanks for having him.
他想来  我随时欢迎
Oh, I will take him as much as he'll have it.
让我家孩子也看看什么叫礼貌
Show my own boys what manners look like.
丽贝卡告诉你  他在学校的事了吗
Hey, did Rebecca tell you about his school?
没有  怎么了
No. What happened?
他好像是考试得了很高的分
I guess he scored off the charts on some tests,
现在校方想把他送走
and now they want to uproot him during the school year,
送去私立学院什么的
send him to some private academy.
把他和其他两个孩子分开
You know, take him away from the other two.
为什么  那是个寄宿学校吗
Why? Is it, is it a boarding school?
不是
No.
就是
No, it's, uh--
就是穿制服什么的
it's uniforms and,
身边全都是白人小孩
a lot of little white kids
搞得那里像是在德国纳粹一样
marching around like it's Nazi Germany.
我明白了
Oh, I see.
所以你才向我咨询
That's why you're running this by me.
什么
What?
你想找一个黑人批准你在育儿方面
You're looking for me to give you the black person seal of approval
做一个糟糕的决定
for any messed-up parenting decision you make.
怎么就糟糕了  我只是...
How is it messed up? I just--
不想让我儿子觉得自己更特殊而已
I don't want my son to feel more different.
所以就因为他是黑人  你就想阻碍他的发展
Okay, so you just want to hold him back because he's black?
不  当然不是了
No. Absolutely not. I...
杰克
Jack,
兰德尔是个特别的孩子
Randall is special.
如果你让他放弃如此好的一个机会
So, if you're looking for somebody to make you feel better
还期待别人会来安慰你
about denying him a special opportunity,
你还是另找一位黑人吧
you may just have to find yourself another black person.
再见了  伙计们
See you, guys.
准备好啦
Ready, Freddy.
再见  伊薇特夫人
Bye, Ms. Yvette.
-赢了吗  -当然
- Did you win? - Yep.
当我把她的孩子送到她怀里时
And I'll never forget the look on her face
她的表情我永生难忘
when I placed her child back into her arms.
永生难忘
Never.
这就是我的工作
So, yeah, that's what I do.
日复一日地
Day in and day out,
将像你们这样的孩子从火里救出来
I save children, just like you guys, from fires.
谢谢
Thank you.
大家为肯德尔的妈妈曼迪鼓掌
Let's give it up for Kendal's mom, Mandy! Yeah.
下一位是苔丝的爸爸  兰德尔
All right, okay, uh, up next is Tess's dad, Randall,
他是位气象员
who is a weatherman.
抱歉抱歉
Oh, sorry, sorry.
说错了
Uh, strike that.
他是位天气交易员
He's a weather trader.
我不知道这是干什么的  听他解释吧
I don't know what that is, but I think he's gonna tell us.
欢迎兰德尔
Here's Randall.
你们好
Hey, y'all.
我是天气交易员
I'm a weather trader,
我知道这个很难解释
which I know can be a little bit hard to explain,
于是
and so, um,
我给你们写了首歌
I wrote you guys a song about it.
爸爸不是不会弹钢琴吗
I thought Daddy couldn't play the piano?
爸爸的确不会啊
Daddy cannot.
*如果你*
*If you*
等等  等一下  抱歉
Wait, mm, hold on one second. Sorry about that.
天呐
Oh, sweet Jesus.
若你...
If you...
请稍等
Mm. One second, please.
*若你有家农场*
*If you've got a farm*
*你该知道玉米未来的成本*
*You should know the future cost of corn*
*所以签一个承包合同*
*So buy yourself a contract to*
*保护自己的庄稼吧*
*Protect your crops.*
*骤雨  风暴或降雪*
*Rain, storm or snow*
*也许会影响*
*Might affect your*
*夏日作物收成  那么*
*Summer crops, so*
*明智地投资*
*Invest your money wisely*
*你就得以安全...*
*You'll be safe...*
大家一起来
Come on everybody.
*若你有家农场*
*If you've got a farm*
*你便知道玉米未来的成本*
*You should know the future cost of corn*
*所以签一个承包合同*
*So buy yourself a contract*
别看他  别看
Look away. Just look away.
*保护自己的庄稼吧*
*To protect your crops.*
你在这里啊
Ah, there you are.
我刚和格蕾丝在一起
I was with Grace.
谁
Who?
格蕾丝  弗兰克的妻子
Grace. Frank's wife.
为什么
Why?
因为她很悲伤  她丈夫过世了
Because she's sad. Her husband died.
你为什么跟我凶
Why are you mad at me?
因为我们不该来的
Because we shouldn't be here.
这不是一场戏
This is not a play.
她是一个真实的人
You know, she's a real person.
我也是一个真实的人
I'm a real person.
我能看出来  终于看出来了
Yeah, I can see that-- maybe for the first time.
你经历过什么
What happened to you?
我父亲过世了
What happened is my dad died.
就是这样
That's what.
而我因此痛恨他
And I hated him for it.
我曾一个月无法进食
And I couldn't eat for a month,
我曾每日醒来以泪洗面
and I used to wake myself up crying,
这样就可以再次在泪水中入眠
so I could cry myself back to sleep again.
这就是我的经历
That's what happened.
你为什么将这些情感撇开
Why do you push all of that away?
这些不是你害怕的妖怪
You can't just kill the feelings
你无法扼杀自己的情绪
like they're some creature that you're afraid of.
这种痛楚是你的一部分
That pain is a part of you.
我现在能看出来
I can see it now.
也能感觉到
I can feel it.
抱歉  吃过腌菜
Sorry, pickle mouth.
我不介意
I don't care.
杰玛还好吗
Is Jemma OK?
什么  她很好
What? She's fine.
她说今天和你相处得很愉快
She said she had a really nice day with you.
但我根本不信
Which I didn't believe for a second,
因为你没有回来  所以我追问了她
because you didn't come back, so I pressed.
丢下她  我很抱歉
I am really sorry that I left her.
如果你想以遗弃儿童罪起诉
I can understand if you want to press charges
我可以理解
for child abandonment.
天呐  快别这么说
God, don't even worry about it.
我自己还曾把她丢在三大百货
I've left her at Three Malls myself,
而且不止一次在高速路上
and I've wanted to shove her out of the car
想把她从车里丢出去
on the freeway at least once.
我都不知道拿她怎么办了
I don't know what to do with her anymore.
我走不进她的内心
I can't reach her.
昨天之前
Before yesterday,
她在两周里只和我说过七个字
she's spoken seven words to me in two weeks.
你也听到了
And you heard them:
"你雇了个胖子啊"
"I see you hired the fat one."
这是你雇我的原因吗
Is that why you hired me?
不  天呐  当然不是
No! God, no.
不全是这样
Not entirely.
我猜就是
Yeah, I thought so.
我也知道这样不好
I am not proud of it.
我很抱歉  但那真不是唯一的原因
I am sorry and it's really not the only reason.
见你本人之前  我就很喜欢你的简历
I-I liked your resume before I met you.
但  确实
But, yeah.
我觉得你可能会...
I thought that maybe you'd be able to...
理解她
understand her.
理解她的问题
Her issues.
天呐  我这样说出来
Oh, my God, it sounds horrible
太伤人了
when I say it out loud.
天呐  拜托别辞职
God, please don't quit.
别再让我处理私人事务了
No more personal stuff.
你看到我工作  了解我的能力了
You saw my work; you know I can do it.
别再让我开车带杰玛了
No more driving Jemma around.
你可以雇一个助手代劳的
You can afford an assistant for that.
-成交  -我要加入蝴蝶舞会
- Done. - And I want to chair the Butterfly Ball.
-可以  -我还要一间办公室
- It's yours. - And I want an office.
-没问题  -我还想要一个实习生
- Okay. - And I want an intern.
好吧  太过了
Okay, too far.
明天九点见
I'll see you at 9:00 tomorrow.
谢谢
Thank you.
杰玛还在这里吗
Hey, is Jemma still here?
在外面
She's outside.
好的
Okay.
喂喂  皮尔森公司
Hello? Hello? Pearson Corporation.
想谈一单大生意吗
Would you like to discuss the big deal?
我太忙了  你回头打给我吧
Well, I'm too busy. You'll have to call back.
喜欢过来和爸爸一起工作  是不是
You love coming to work with Dad, huh?
我想让你来帮我一些忙
I wanted you here because I need your help with something.
过来
Come here.
这是什么
What's that?
这是公司负责在建的房子
That is a house the company's working on.
-真酷  -是啊
- Cool. - Yeah.
你看
You see, uh...
你看  我不知道  建这面墙需要多少
You see, I don't know how many feet of two-by-four
宽四寸厚二尺的板材
I'm gonna need for this wall right here.
你知道三英尺是多少...
You see how each... how each inch is...
多少英寸吗
is three feet?
22.5英尺
22h feet.
真了不起  小家伙
That's pretty cool, buddy.
没想到你数学这么好
Didn't know you were so good with numbers.
等等  过来
Wait, wait, wait. Come here.
那这面墙呢
What about this wall right here?
建这面墙需要多少
How many... how many do I need for that?
这个我不会算
I don't know that one.
一秒钟前你还会算  现在不会了吗
You knew how do it a second ago, now you don't?
我不知道  爸爸
I don't know it, Dad.
你肯定会算
I think you do.
我不会
I don't.
兰德尔  别闹了
Randall, that's enough.
-过来  -我不想算
- Come here. - I don't want to.
看  就是这面墙
Look. This wall, right here.
我需要多少板材
How much do I need?
-我不知道  不知道  -把答案说出来
- I don't know. I don't know. - Tell me the answer.
多少英尺  快告诉我
How many feet? Tell me right now.
我不知道
I don't know.
见鬼  兰德尔  快说答案
Damn, it, Randall, tell me the answer!
34英尺
34.
说什么
What's that?
34英尺
34.
很正确
That's right.
你为什么要假装不会算这些题呢
Why are you pretending not to know this stuff, huh?
故意在数学中考个B
Getting B's in math?
不让别人知道你很聪明
Not letting people see how smart you are?
我不想和他们不一样
I don't want to be different from them.
和谁不一样  学校里那些孩子吗
Different from who? Who, the kids at school?
如果得了A  我就有冰激凌吃
If... if I get an A, I'll get ice cream,
而凯特和凯文没有
and Kate and Kevin won't.
他们会恨我的
And then they'll hate me.
我能跟你说实话吗
Can I be honest with you?
男人间的对话
Man to man?
你妈妈和我总是尽力
You know, your mom and me, we always try
对你们几个一视同仁
to treat you kids the same.
一向如此
Always have.
但并不总是有效
Hasn't always worked, because, well,
因为你们本来就不一样
you're not all the same.
你是我们领养的  我们没好好谈过这事
You're adopted, and we don't talk about that enough.
因为对我来说  你完全就是我儿子
'Cause to me, you are every part my son.
也许...我不想让你觉得自己太突出
Maybe I.. I don't want you to feel like you stand out.
但是你得知道一件事
But I need you to know something.
我希望你出类拔萃
I want you to stand out.
我希望你们每一个都能
I want all of you to be as different
与众不同
as you can possibly be.
做最好的自己
In all the best ways.
我倾尽全力爱你  孩子
I love you as much as a human heart can, kiddo.
你是个出众的年轻人
You are an exceptional young man.
别让你爸卑微的想法
So don't let your dad's poor choice
阻碍你展现自我
make you feel afraid to be different.
好吗
Okay?
好
Okay.
把手指放上去弹弹  声音更美妙
It sounds better when you put your fingers on it.
在电影里
You know how, in the movies,
主角不擅长一件事
when somebody's bad at something,
但又不想这样
but they don't want to be,
于是就下定决心练习
and so they set their mind to it.
然后通过蒙太奇的剪辑手法
And then we see this montage
无数遍的练习镜头呈现在观众眼前
of them practicing and practicing.
而到了最后的关键时刻  就会大放异彩
And then comes the big moment, and they're amazing,
大家欢呼喝彩
and everybody cheers.
我看过这类电影
I've seen a few movies like that, yeah.
我可能跳过了"蒙太奇"部分
I think I skipped the montage.
你第一次告诉我你的工作时
When you first told me what you did for a living,
天  我一个字也听不懂
man, I didn't understand a word.
对天发誓
Hand to God, I mean,
你还不如说些德语什么的
you might as well have been speaking German.
但当时我看着你的表情
But I was watching your face.
我没吸毒的时候  我曾与几位
In my better days, I have met and played with
世界顶级音乐家一起演奏过
some of the greatest musicians in the world.
当他们谈起音乐
And when they talked about music,
他们的表情看起来
their face looked like your face
和你谈起工作时的表情一模一样
when you told me about whatever the hell it is you do.
但是如果有帮助  我可以教你弹一两段琴
But if it'll help, I can show you a thing or two on the piano.
那就太棒了
That would be great.
-今晚就算了  -对啊
- Oh, not tonight, just... - Oh, right.
-现在太晚了  -是啊  算了
- It's late is the thing. - Yeah. No.
我明白
I got ya.
晚安
Good night.
Night.
你不用和我告别
You don't have to say bye to me.
我没辞职
I didn't quit.
我明白你的感受
I know what you're going through.
别想着和我促膝谈心了
Stop trying to have a moment with me.
我妈以前很苗条  也很漂亮
So, my mom was skinny and gorgeous.
现在也很漂亮
Well, is gorgeous.
大家还是喜欢搭讪她
She still gets hit on by everyone.
有一次她得了流感  还被人问起
She once was asked if she was a model
是不是模特儿
when she had the flu.
在这样的妈妈身边长大非常艰难
Pretty hard growing up with a mom like that.
我一直不断拿自己和她作比较
I spent all my time comparing myself to her,
然后把气撒在她身上
and then I took it out on her.
现在我们几乎不说话了  很糟糕
And now we barely talk, and it sucks.
你妈不完美
Hey, your mom's not perfect.
她有她的问题  你有你的问题  但是
She has her stuff, and you have yours, but...
你别再跟她对着干了
you got to cut her a break.
不然你会后悔的
Or you're gonna regret it.
我保证
I promise.
凯特  能配合一下吗
Kate, will you please help me out?
不  我讨厌这件裙子
No, I hate this dress!
我知道  可是我不管你讨不讨厌
I know. I don't care that you hate it, though.
就这一件合身的干净衣服
It's what's clean and what fits,
-你穿定这件了  -我恨你
- and it's what you're wearing. - I hate you!
快穿上  我们要迟到了
Put it on, please; we're running late.
杰克
Hey, Jack?
-兰德尔  你们准备好了吗  -好了
- Randall? You guys are ready? - Yeah.
-五分钟后得出发了  -我知道  有我呢
- We have to leave in five minutes. - I know. I got him.
你确定吗
You sure about this?
对  我确定
Yeah, I'm sure.
听你妈妈的话
Hey, listen to your mother.
你看上去棒极了
See, you look great.
拿好你的午饭  小姑娘
Come get your lunch, young lady.
谢谢
Thank you.
-看清没有  -嗯
- See it? - Yeah.
需要点时间练习
Yeah. Takes a little time,
不过你会掌握窍门的
but you'll get the hang of it.
看着我
Here, look at me.
真精神
Looking sharp.
准备好上学第一天了吗
You ready for your first day?
凯特和凯文会跟我们一起走吗
Are Kate and Kevin gonna ride with us?
我们先把他们送到学校
We're gonna drop them off,
然后再把你送到学校
then we're gonna drop you off,
放学后  我们再一起回家
and then we'll all be back together
-好吗  -好
- after school, okay? - Okay.
等等  过来
Hey, wait. Come here.
往下系点
We'll tuck this low.
这样好看又舒服
Nice and comfortable.
去跟你妈说再见
Say bye to your mom.
新鲜出炉的煎饼来了
Hot, plump ones coming through.
妈  今天放学后我要去练足球
Mom, I have a soccer practice after school today.
我记得
Yeah, I remember.
过来
Come on.
我有话要说
I have something to say.
我父亲每天都会系领带
Uh... my dad put on a tie every day
因为他必须这样做
because he had to.
我每天系领带  是因为我想这样
I put one on every day because I want to.
这点很重要
It's important you know that.
也许我不用每天靠出入火场来维持生计
Maybe I don't run into burning buildings for a living,
但对我来说  我的工作同样惊险刺激
but to me, my work is challenging and exciting.
也许别人很难理解
I will not apologize for the fact
但我不会因此道歉
that it's hard to explain to people.
好的  老爸
Okay, Daddy.
还有  威廉
Uh, also, William,
谢谢你愿意教我弹钢琴
thank you for offering to teach me piano,
但我觉得
but I don't think at this point
鉴于我们现在的关系
in our relationship it would be healthy
还是先别这么做了
to introduce that dynamic.
所以
And so,
下周二开始  我要去上
starting next Tuesday, I'm gonna be taking piano lessons
帕金斯女士的钢琴课
from Mrs. Perkins down the road.
春天会有一场演奏会
There's gonna be a recital in the spring,
我希望你们都能来支持我
and I hope that you will all come and support me in this.
刚才是怎么回事
What was that?
那是中年危机  亲爱的
That was a midlife crisis, baby.
这还不算什么  接着吃华夫饼吧
But just a little one, so go on, eat your waffle.
"还不算什么"  说得真好
"Just a little one." That's good.
他竟然要学钢琴
He-He's gonna take piano?
给你买了杯咖啡
Brought you a cappuccino.
牛奶换成豆奶  对吗
Soy, yeah?
你太贴心了
You're too kind.
我还想说...
Also wanted to say that, uh...
我想说  我原谅你了
You know, I wanted to say that I forgive you.
那节"课"的事...
For the lesson. Um...
我能说什么呢  奏效了
What can I say? It worked.
我觉得也是
Mm, I'd say it did.
不过课可不止那一节
But, um, that's not the only lesson.
不是吗  好吧
No? Okay.
我们之间发生的事...
What happened between you and me...
永远不会再发生了
is never gonna happen again.
我以为...
Oh. I-I thought...
我知道  但我们仅仅只是这种关系
I know you did, but this is who we are and all we are.
你是我丈夫  我是你的亡妻
You're my husband, and I'm your dead wife.
你永远不会再和她上床了
And you will never sleep with her again.
这让你作何感想
Now, how does that make you feel?
悲伤
Sad.
好极了
Great.
用上这种情绪
Use that.
我加入
I'm in.
三个小家伙之家
那隐形传输是怎么回事
So what was that about teleportation?
隐形传输和冷空气
Yeah, the teleportation and the freeze breath
或是热空气
or, like, hot breath.
玩得开心
Hey, have fun.
再见  爸爸
Bye, Dad.
爱你
Love you.